Welcome
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): back to Candace, everyone. My name is Ian Carroll, and welcome to the first episode where I'll be filling in for Candace while she spends time with baby Roman. Later on, we'll have updates on Candace and baby Roman, and a crazy story of her hospital being evil. Also, Trump goes after Big Pharma, Diddy starts his trial, and claims the freak-offs were all consensual, and the internet is losing its mind over Macron and his buddies allegedly getting caught with a baggie of coke. But first, a scandal that started at kids' birthday parties at Urban Air Adventure Parks
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): is blowing up in a massive way. And one mom who spent the last three years fighting against a multi-billion dollar private equity monster is about to top with a whole house of cards. All that and more
Speaker 2: right now on Candace.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): so imagine your mom or a dad and you want to take your kids to the adventure park for a fun day maybe a birthday party right
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): um that's where today's story starts with a young girl seven years old being taken by her parents to urban air adventure park and they were expecting just a normal day. They are expecting a wonderful day with their kid. And...
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): If you've ever been to Urban Air, you would know that there's all kinds of crazy things for the kids to do. And, theoretically, their staff kind of help them keep them safe, help them run the rides. And this little girl teed up to get on one
Speaker 4: of the most popular rides at Urban Air. We have video from that day.
Ready? Go! I want to go back. You got
Speaker 5: it.
We
Speaker 6: want you to get drunk. Now
this is
Speaker 7: called the Skyrider attraction, and it's going to play a big part in today's story. But I just
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): wanted to jump in really quickly and give you a disclaimer that the next part of this clip is pretty traumatic. And it doesn't show anything extremely graphic, but if you're a parent or you have young kids, this is going to be very hard to watch and listen to because...
They
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): were not expecting their day to go like this.
- Are you
Speaker 8: okay? Yeah, are you okay? - Sweet, are you okay? - Sweet, are you
okay? Are you
Speaker 9: okay? Somebody go 911 now!
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): So, that little girl, unfortunately, suffered a punctured lung, a traumatic brain injury, broken bones, and permanent disability, including learning deficits, hearing loss, and her injuries are still uncertain and sustained to this day. They have been in secret arbitration up until right now. And...
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): This is just one poor little girl's story at Urban Air, but unfortunately, it is very much not the only story like this. And today, I
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): wanted to tell you a story about Urban Air, because Urban Air is a very small piece of a very big picture, and it starts...
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): with a man named michael browning in 2011 he founds this company called urban air and it's an adventure park right and he's growing urban air adventure parks um you know with the goal of being a big shot like his dad i would presume he eventually in 2018 gets a whole bunch of private equity funding and expands his business rapidly all around the united states from 45 parks at the time up well over a hundred
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): They initially got investment from Ross Perot's private equity firm, MPK Partners, and they took them from just a small business
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): in the Indianapolis area to a nationwide chain, and they started franchising. Franchising allowed Michael Browning Jr. to invest.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): expand this business out and allow other people to buy into his franchise and to have urban airs opening all
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): around the country and to have those businesses opened by local people that wanted to change their lives and their community by starting a business and buying into the urban air franchise. This is the story of franchising, and it is the bedrock of the American economy in a lot of ways, because it's a fundamental way that people
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): start a business and not only change their own lives and their family's lives, but also elevate their community. Franchising, unfortunately, has taken a pretty dark turn in the last 10 years, and we are going
to come
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): back to that theme over and over and over again throughout this story. Because as Urban Air expanded, lawsuits started to flood in because of the way that things were being done.
And
Speaker 10: Michael Browning has had some choice words that are posted on his website to say about those lawsuits. But as we dig this
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): story open, you'll see that Michael Browning's words are, well, I'll just read them for you. Quote, this is not a franchise where I'm sitting back at my desk in some ivory tower and collecting royalties and teaching you a theory. I'm in the trenches, experiencing what the franchisees are experiencing.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): That is huge for our core and our motto.
Right on,
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Michael.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Good to know. It's
also good to
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): know that, let's just say we have
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): documentation that seems to imply that that Skyrider attraction, that zipline type of thing that that poor girl fell off of, that was not originally created by Urban Air. And there's documentation that seems to
Speaker 10: imply that, in fact, Michael Browning Jr., shall we say, filed patents after signing a confidentiality agreement?
Speaker 10: with the original company that founded it,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Leap of Faith Adventures. If you search the internet for Leap of Faith Adventures today, you will find just about nothing because Leap of Faith Adventures no longer exists. And that's another dig for another time. But let's just say that the emails, correspondences, and documentation that we have
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): kind of implies what might have happened to Leap of Faith Adventures. Because when you're founding a national chain of adventure parks, you need all kinds of cool rides and attractions and stuff for the kids to do, like rock walls and zip lines and crazy trampolines spin around tumblers and stuff like that. And it sounds pretty dangerous because it can be, right? And when you take your kid
Speaker 10: out to a park like that, you're expecting them to be providing the safety so that your kids can have a fun, safe
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): time
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): out. Once Michael Browning Jr. had expanded his empire of trampoline and adventure parks all around the nation, he realized that he was onto something and he could expand and do even more. So following a trend that is rampant in private equity right now, in 2021, Browning decided to scale up following a hot new trend in private equity that gets referred to as
Speaker 10: platforms, where
the
They
Speaker 10: will buy up different companies that are in the same niche, in the same sector, so that if
you
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): wanted to fix up your house, they've got AC people, they've got cleaning people, they've got painting people. This is just one example, but it happens in all sorts of different areas of our economy. And Michael Browning Jr. decided that
He was
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): going to take on the niche that was all things children. Why not apply the private equity playbook of cutting costs, streamlining businesses, and maximizing profits to all businesses' children? So
that's what
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): he did.
And
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): he bought up a number of businesses in rapid succession with backing from his private equity buddies, including Sylvan Learning Centers, Waterwing, Snapology, XP League, Class 101, Premier Martial Arts, and The Little Gym. But among all brands, it has 1,200 locations
Speaker 10: across the country and serves 25 million children a year. It generates $1.1 billion in annual revenue. Michael Browning Jr. seems to be doing pretty good. But...
Speaker 10: But problems started to arise as they acquired each of these companies, and they didn't start with The Little Gym, but our story starts at The Little Gym today. Founded originally
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): by Robin West and Robin McCoy, and I just want to show you their faces because I get the feeling we'll come back to them in the future.
But...
The
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): story really comes to a head when Tiffany Sianci enters the picture. And Tiffany Sianci bought into this franchise as a mom that was doing other business and wanted to spend more time with her kids around 2017. And so she thought that buying one of these franchises would be a great service to her community and a great way to spend more time with her kids because her kids could attend the little gyms.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): And if you've not been to the little gym, it's a space for children of all types, but particularly targeted children that have special types of needs, whether that be auditory, sensory, learning, cognitive, whatever. It's a gym for all types of children to do gymnastics and learn through physical movement. And Tiffany Sianci really found her passion there. We're going to be drawing from...
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): news reporting and articles that have reported on Tiffany's story over the last three years, as it has gotten crazy. And just recently, it's gone to a whole new level, as cases against Urban Air and the parent company, Unleashed Brands, have moved from secret arbitration into public court, as well as since Tiffany Cianci and several
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): other insiders have decided that enough is enough, and it's time to come clean. Cianci started
back
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): in 2017 and all was gravy it was a wonderful time and a wonderful business for her to run and she was very successful
Speaker 10: at it but then right around the buyout with unleashed brands
corporate came
Speaker 10: down to her and said hey we have this new advising partner and they're going
to help
Speaker 10: us with this new stuff and and they were presented as though they were just going to advise them
And
Speaker 10: slowly, little by little, it became apparent to Cianci and the rest of the staff that this was not an
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): advisor, this was a buyout. And the buyout was Unleashed Brands. And the advisor they were speaking to was Michael Browning Jr. himself. Suffice it to say that Cianci and many of the other franchise owners were uncomfortable with the various changes that were being made.
The types of changes that would separate Cianci and many of the other franchise owners were uncomfortable with the various changes that were being made.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): The people running these gyms from their clients, things like call centers, where when a parent calls with a concern about their child, they get a person
in a
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): call center halfway across the country instead of the actual teachers that work with their child every day. You could see how that could be a little bit of an issue when you're dealing with special needs kids doing gymnastics, but that's not really how private equity plays.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): So, Sianci organized her fellow franchise owners into an association, sort of like a union, to push back against the changes and to stand
up for
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): the franchisee rights. Just to clarify, a franchisee is the person that founded the small business, the owner of the franchise. The franchisor is the big boys, the corporates, Michael Browning Jr. in this case. Over the next three years and to this day,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Unleashed Brands took Tiffany Sianci through legal, uh, can
I say hell? Yeah, you
Speaker 11: can say hell.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Cool.
Over the next
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): three years, Unleashed Brands took Tiffany Sianci through legal hell, dragging
her into
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): hundreds of thousands of debt through untold emotional and financial hardships, through the most insane journey of just outright unethical,
Speaker 10: unlawful lawfare. Yeah.
This
Speaker 10: is not unique to Tiffany or unique to Unleash Brands or unique to the Little Jim. Franchises are all across America and they are all kinds of businesses that support a huge sector of our economy. And franchises in particular are in the crosshairs of private equity today because they can be so incredibly profitable for reasons that we will go into.
Speaker 10: Suffice it to say, when you are outsourcing so much of your business,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): cost, debt, and the actual running of your day-to-day business to individual people, to families, and small business owners, you can offload a lot of risk and a lot of the hardship and just suck all the money up to the top.
So Tiffany has
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): been in arbitration, which is a secret court system where all the rules work differently. All the judges work differently. Everything is for profit and everything is secret by definition. She's been in arbitration for the last three years. And we have
now got
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): information.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): through her and others, that there are many, many other people. We're talking hundreds of other people in arbitration just with Unleash Brands, let alone with other private equity and other corporations around the world. The big picture problem with this whole story is not just that private equity is buying up and taking advantage of small businesses, not just that private equity is
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): applying the private equity playbook to these businesses that are focused on kids, mind you, but that those practices that private equity uses are inherently counter to safety. Tiffany gave this quote to the New York Times. That might be okay when you're cleaning a dryer vent, but it's not when you're throwing around a four-month-old and you need them to be safe. Ms. Sianci said he was moving faster than we would need to get to know the business, referring to the changes happening at the little gym. And the key word there
is
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): is safe. And as the clip that we opened this segment shows, safety is obviously not the first thing on the mind of Unleash Brands and of Urban Air. But that is just one video. And there are many other videos from Urban Air. Again, we are going to blur out the most sensitive parts of these videos, but we just wanted to get you a sense of what you can find just on YouTube if you go searching for this type of stuff.
Speaker 12 (lower-pitched voice): Florida family is suing after their son fell from a zip line at an amusement park. A word of warning, the video may be disturbing to some viewers. Now you can see the 10 year old come around the corner and then fall 20 feet from the zip line. The accident happened in September at Urban Air Trampoline and Adventure Park in Lakeland. An investigation by the Florida Department of Agriculture found the boy's harness was not properly secured at the time of the incident.
Speaker 12 (lower-pitched voice): Urban Air says the employees involved in the incident don't work there anymore and others have been retrained. So
there's
Speaker 13: examples of kids falling, but there's also examples
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): of adults and parents getting hurt. In the next video, a mom almost died in front of her own daughter at their birthday party. The
Speaker 14: video is shocking. Ever!
Speaker 14: A mom is hanging by her neck, helpless, as she finds herself trapped on an indoor zip line. Time is running out. She's in real danger of choking to death. It happened after she says the harness apparently came loose and slipped around her neck.
Speaker 15: It seemed as if they put the harness in correctly. Instead of strapping it under my arms, it seemed as if they strapped it.
Speaker 15: up here.
Speaker 14: She suffered rope burns and bruises around her neck. Evelyn Rapier is now suing the park, alleging negligence and improper maintenance of the ride. And
so
Speaker 16: when things like this happen, the park gets sued, which is owned by a small business owner,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): but they're just trying to comply with corporate. Corporate, unleashed brands, pushes all responsibility down onto the park and anything else that they can't wash away gets filed away into secret arbitration. and you agree to secret arbitration
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): when you sign your kid in at the park when you sign those waivers. Because if you didn't
Speaker 10: know, almost every waiver you sign these days, whether you're going to the rock climbing gym or you're signing up for some swimming lesson or you're just buying a washing machine, almost all of those waivers include what's
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): called an arbitration agreement. And that is where you agree to waive your rights to court
And
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): instead agree to settle in arbitration, which is essentially secret court, where the judges are all for sale. We're going to get into arbitration way more in coming episodes, but suffice to say that it's a great way to cover up all
Speaker 10: sorts of nefarious stuff if you
don't want
Speaker 10: the public to know. You might have noticed too.
that
Speaker 10: the woman in that video made purposeful note that the harness
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): didn't seem to be put on correctly. And that's because these rides are not staffed correctly because A, Urban Air hires children under the age of 18, 16 and 17 year olds. And you would think that you'd need a couple of them to staff these rides, but there's documentation that seems to show that, quote,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Michael discussed reducing the number of attendants from two to one on the Skyrider attraction, stating that eliminating an employee from an attraction can save a park $10,000 per year. That very same weekend in Ahwatukee, the Skyrider attraction had one employee working when a major accident occurred.
In
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): LOFA's opinion, this short-term cost segmentality is a major concern. You might notice LOFA is Leap of Faith Adventures. The company that I had mentioned had originally designed this ride.
The company that I
Speaker 10: had mentioned, it appeared that maybe Unleashed Brands and Michael Browning Jr. might have done something nefarious to take
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): that patent and that
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): attraction from leap of faith adventures and now leap of faith adventures is unfortunately no more but this document as well as several others that we have are actually from when leap of faith adventures took them to court because they were not okay with what was being done with their rides the ways they were being set up the ways they were being run and they made specific claims about what was going on that's not to mention that there's
Speaker 10: evidence that seems to suggest both human testimony as well as email testimony were
Speaker 10: that Unleashed Brands was flying in Chinese nationals to put together their adventure parks because it was cheaper than paying American labor. You know, doesn't really strike me as the kind of thing that's safe when you're putting together all sorts of rides and dangerous equipment that children are going to be playing on, but it is cheaper. I'll
give him that.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): So,
what
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Tiffany Sianci and all of the other franchisees at the Little Gym have been through has been horrendous. It has been a multi-year process of intimidation and of coercion and of very complicated changes to their businesses that do not benefit them or their children. At least that's how they see it. But
So
Speaker 10: there's a darker and deeper side of the story. And that's when you start to realize that private equity is a team. It's a club and they are all friends together and none of them really want the boat to be rocked. And so when Tiffany started rocking the boat, when Tiffany stood up to these people and organized with her other
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): franchisees, and then when she wouldn't go away and be silenced, they decided that they were going to make an example out of her.
And
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): they have done a number
Speaker 10: of things over the years, things that are almost unspeakable.
And we don't have
Speaker 10: time to speak of all of them because there are so many, but perhaps the most unspeakable, or at least
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): the most, uh, inhumane that was done to Tiffany was captured in court during one of her depositions. And I'm going to let
her speak for
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): herself, but I do want you to know that this is going
to be hard
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): to watch, especially if you're a mother
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Um, but this
Speaker 17: is what happened to Tiffany Cianci.
- You
Speaker 18: might also say that there are very likely instances of significant emotional distress related to somebody trying to expedite me having an abortion the day I lost my
daughter. -
Speaker 19: Are you seeking that here in this
case? - I
Speaker 19: would say yes. - And again, are you talking to the recent miscarriage where, uh, the parties worked with you
to
Speaker 20: reschedule your deposition?
Speaker 20: Worked with me? You tried to depose me in
labor.
Speaker 21: You tried to depose me while I was in bed bleeding.
I had
Speaker 21: contractions
Speaker 22: two minutes apart.
So no, I would not say
Speaker 22: you worked with me.
I would say it
Speaker 23: was vulgar and inhuman. I was copied on the emails where you asked that I be compelled. I was copied on the email where you asked
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): That I make sure that I had the fastest abortion possible when my doctor's note said that I was Catholic and meeting with my priest to avoid
it. I was
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): certainly copied when you said you, Miss Sixkiller, said that you thought that me bleeding
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): Baseball sized. Baseball sized blood clots and having contractions two minutes apart wouldn't be too stressful for me in that state and you thought I should be deposed for 18 hours. This is two weeks later and I am still having contractions and I am sitting here so that I don't have to see
Speaker 21: you again.
So
Speaker 21: yes, I would say I was copied and it was harmful. We would have moved the
Speaker 25: hearing date out further to further accommodate you. So I apologize. No, no, no, that's not true, that is not true. When you
Speaker 27: found out I lost my baby, within 30 minutes of getting the note, 30 minutes of getting the note, you said you wanted me produced for deposition in labor pre-surgery. I'm going to move to strike.
Speaker 27: You said that you wanted him to order me to have the fastest available procedure in the state of Maryland. And if you'd been in court, you would have been referred for disciplinary action, but we're in arbitration. So here we are. And yes, it was a damage emotionally to me. And I think I'm pretty sure you're a mom. It would have been emotionally damaging to you.
So that's
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): where we wound up all because Michael Browning
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Jr. wanted to be a big boy like his daddy.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): and run a giant empire of children's focused franchises.
Speaker 10: And when those franchises spoke up and said that this is not how you run a toddler gym, this is not how you run a martial arts academy, they stomped down. The problem was they stomped
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): down on the wrong woman. And Tiffany Sianci would
not give up
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): and would not die. And she is still fighting to this day. And by
Speaker 10: the way, those email chains that she mentioned,
-
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah.
we
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): got them and they're all right there. And yes, they do clearly say exactly what Tiffany was alleging on that stand in that deposition. And a running theme throughout this whole thing will be that
Speaker 10: when you're in arbitration, let's just
say there's
Speaker 10: not really consequences for lying as long as you're on the team of the big boys. There's not really consequences for your lawyers not following the law, for the judges not following the law, because it's all a system for profit and it's all being paid for and one team has millions
Speaker 10: and millions and millions of dollars to throw at the lawsuit. And the other team is guaranteed
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): to go hundreds of thousands of dollars into debt until they can't fight anymore and are forced to give up and give
in. But
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Tiffany took to TikTok
a few
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): years ago, and I found her story way back then early on, and she has been fighting ever since. And she's fought all alone for much of it. But eventually she grew a little bit of support and a little bit more and a little bit and she's won enough of her cases
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): including a defamation suit by now, that now there's all of this new documentation coming out. Almost everything that we've shown today has never been out before. And there is way more where that came from. And there are way more people involved in this thing ready to talk about it because this goes not just all across Unleashed Brands and throughout many of their businesses, but this goes well beyond Unleashed Brands out into the entire private equity world. Because when you give billionaire businesses like these private equity monsters There's
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): sort of a free reign to stomp all over the little guy, you better believe they're going to take that opportunity and run all the way to the bank with it. And they've been running to the bank with it for so long that let's just say the little guys
have had
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): enough. So that
is where
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Tiffany stands today. She is currently in court and there's a lot more to talk about as far as what's going on there. But...
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): We just heard just recently that one of these secret arbitrations, because all of these cases of children getting hurt, falling off of rides at the adventure park, as well as Tiffany's entire case in secret arbitration about her toddler gym, all of it's in secret. And so none of them could speak up until just recently. And so all these guys, the team over
Speaker 10: at Unleashed Brands, Michael Browning Sr.,
who
Speaker 10: is not just daddy, he's on some of those filings, Norman Leon, Michael Browning Jr., Laura Sixkiller, Stephen Polozzola, all these guys that are written on all these forms that are involved in all these depositions that are on these cases, they're going to come back up. And we're just going to look at what they did and what they're doing and see why would you do that? Because ultimately you should
stay away
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): from our toddlers and you should stay away from our little chimps. And we want our kids to grow up in a place where
They
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): can be treated like children and not like numbers for profit. So that's the
start of
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): that story
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): for now. That's all we got for today. Before we get to an update about Candice and the hospital and how it all
went with
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): baby Roman, I want to tell you about our first sponsor, GNO Land. If you're into the world of computer programming, you need to check out
my friends
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): at gno.land. GNO is a distributed multi-user virtual computer implemented
on top
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): of the blockchain so that every operation occurs in a predestined way.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): user program code and memory states are made tamper-proof by the use of merkle trees and consensus-based verification all provided by the underlying blockchain storage layer itself distributed gno unifies the concepts in a single concept the realm each realm is like an always active process running forever for example as a web server in a regular system
A
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): live process is defined by its PID, its memory, and the set of system resources it uses at a given time. Similarly, in a GNO, a Realm is defined by its identity and its global memory state, which may contain, for example, the amount of coins it detains. The Realm is decentralized and put back in control of the developer. The operating system itself becomes transparent. Realm processes are both resource users and providers, with full control and accountability. Learn more at gno.land. That's gno.land today.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): What if I told you that you could cut your cell phone bill in half and support a U.S. company who shares your values? Values like supporting our local veterans and creating American jobs. What if I told you that you don't have to sacrifice coverage because you'll be on America's most dependable 5G network? I'm talking about the only wireless company that Candice endorses, Pure Talk, a wireless company that is veteran-led and invests in a U.S. customer service team so that you have the best support possible. If you're with Verizon, AT&T, or T-Mobile,
Join the hundreds of
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): thousands
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): We'll see you next time.
So a
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): brief update from the hospital. Candice gave birth to a beautiful, healthy baby boy, Roman. Could not be happier for her. We're all feeling so good. She is doing well. I just talked to her earlier. Baby Roman is doing great. And they are back from the hospital.
But
Speaker 10: there was a funny incident after the hospital because Candice, naturally, after he had a healthy baby and she was feeling great, she left. Before the recommended 48-hour holding time.
Not
Speaker 10: sure why they need you to stay there for 48 hours and take all their little medicines and get all their ointments that they prescribe. Obviously, she
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): did not give baby Roman all these, you know, shots like hepatitis B, vitamin K, is that for Midasel,
Speaker 28: all these things. Department of Child Services shows up at her house doing a more or less a wellness visit, asking her all sorts of questions. Why did you leave the hospital early? And she wanted to
Speaker 10: clarify when she was communicating the story to us that the person that visited was perfectly nice and just doing their job, but they were doing
it.
Speaker 10: doing the job of going out and more or less pressuring mothers into you should have getting these things and you why are you leaving and it just is a part of this whole pharmaceutical medical complex cartel of pressuring people into
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): getting the drugs getting the shots getting the vaccines and candace obviously being based was like no thanks bye i'm doing great
go
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): away. So Candace will be back at some point to give us updates, to tell us how she's doing. She'll jump into the show from time to time while she's on leave, but she's doing awesome. And she says hi to all of you. So next on to the Diddy trial. Yesterday, the Diddy trial got
Speaker 10: underway to a slightly late start. The jury got sworn in. Opening statements were read. Funny anecdote where the prosecution struck seven black jurors and the defense was trying to call them racist. And it this whole thing, ultimately the judge sustained
their
Speaker 10: motion to strike those jurors. You know, I'm
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): not trying to make a comment on that. I just thought it was funny the way that it got reported on. But then it turned out that victim three
Speaker 10: unknown, we don't know who it is, but victim three apparently is missing. Just a few weeks ago, victim three was,
Speaker 10: came forward or didn't didn't come forward but said that they were willing to testify in the trial um and though we don't know who it is it's obviously was important to the the case because they were going to put victim three on the stand and then just before this all came together and before did he took the stand victim three apparently was out of communication and we do not know where
they are my
Speaker 10: thought
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): immediately went to
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): um, the girl Allie that is sharing all the salacious stuff. I went and looked her up and she's still posting on TikTok as not her. So I don't know what to make of it. I don't know who victim three is. Um, I'm sure we
can all come up with some
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): crazy conspiracy theories about what's going on there. Diddy's side is hoping for a mistrial
just
Speaker 10: because they don't have one of their witnesses. That is extremely unlikely, but it is possibly going to cause
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): some delays and it might actually impact the ability to prosecute Diddy. Um, I presume that Diddy is pulling out
all the
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): stops as we've heard reportings of private investigators looking
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): into people and people being pressured or influenced by his family members and just all sorts of shady, shady, shady, shady, shady. And it's ditty. So what did you expect? It's also worth noting that Maureen Comey, the daughter of James Comey, is on the prosecution team. She also recently served as the lead prosecutor for Ghislaine
Speaker 10: Maxwell. So it's just a funny small club of people up here. And ultimately, that's what I really want to talk about here is that as you might expect, nothing really seems like it's going to come and that's
because
Speaker 10: this is not the case that we were all hoping for them to try. We got on this case. I mean, if you've
been really
Speaker 10: following it since Cassie and before, yeah, there's a lot going on here. But when the Lil Rod lawsuit dropped and most of us kind of caught
wind of
Speaker 10: Diddy and what was going on, the case...
Speaker 10: was that Lil Rod's lawsuit seemed to imply and allege that this was a sexual blackmail operation and that all of Diddy's homes were wired up with secret cameras recording everything that happened and that Lucian Grange and Universal Music Group were named in that lawsuit originally. Except then they mysteriously disappeared off the lawsuit originally.
No
Speaker 10: answers as to why that was the lawyer for little rod
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): that took them off saying that there was no evidence that they were involved. I'm sure that it was just a big mistake that they got named in the first place, despite
Speaker 10: the fact that in the evidence in the testimony or in the allegations in it, like documented.
It
Speaker 10: clearly says that Lucy and Grange was at the parties, that Lucy and Grange had every reason to know what was happening at the parties, that he had private visits with Diddy in the evenings at his home where they disappear into his room for extended periods of time.
But, you know,
Speaker 10: when you're the big boy at the top, you don't get looked into. You don't take the stand. You don't get the dirt on you. And when I was talking to the team earlier...
Speaker 10: They made me aware that I did not even know that there's a whole backstory on Lucian Grange and his big daddy. And oh boy, is that another dig for another day. But I just wanted to point out that the more the Diddy trials progressed, the more they seemed to depart from what was actually really being shown and suspicious in the first place, which was what seemed to be a trafficking ring with what seemed to be blackmail involved with what's absolutely for sure was the...
Speaker 10: uh, shall we say the ex head of security of Michael Jackson, somehow becoming the head of security for a trafficking operation, a blackmail ring for drugs, for whatever he's doing for Diddy. Uh, everything
about this
Speaker 10: operation stank, not to mention the property he had on the border of Mexico. So I'm not too optimistic about what's going to come out of the Diddy trial itself, but I am hoping that
Speaker 10: We'll at least see some dirt thrown on some other celebrities, some cracks open up in other parts of the industry that hopefully will, let's
just say,
Speaker 10: tip over a few dominoes because there's a lot of dominoes ready to fall. And it's worth noting, too, that it's not just the Little Rod lawsuit that has made these allegations. These allegations are widespread in the industry, both from people that have worked alongside Diddy in the music
Speaker 29: world, as well as from bodyguards like Gene Deal.
Speaker 29: Most of those girls, especially if they like
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): mixed drinks, you understand, they see the bottles when they
open them
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): and they trying to keep their eyes on because they don't want to get no kind of drugs put in their system.
But what they
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): don't understand is in the orange juice and it's in the cranberry juice. They done put the pills and the stuff in there, the roofies.
the
Speaker 30 (lower-pitched voice): ecstasy,
Speaker 31: the ease, all, whatever they,
they put it
Speaker 31: in the juice. Yeah, but they don't put
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): it in the baby oil. Don't you worry about it. So that's the Diddy story for now. You're going to think I'm describing weight loss injections, but I'm not. These remarkable weight loss testimonials came from a doctor formulated weight loss supplement called Lean. Patty S. said, I've finally found a weight loss product that works. I wanted to lose 20 pounds and Lean really curves my appetite.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Lori M wrote, I struggled to get weight off and lean has been lifesaver. I've been losing a couple pounds a week or more. And Kelly F said, amazing. I immediately noticed an energy boost and a healthy weight loss in weight. I would promote this product to anyone. Lean was created by a doctor and university researcher to target the goals of GLP-1s, but without the injections. The studied ingredients in lean have been shown to lower blood sugar, radically reduce appetite, and
burn fat
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): by converting it into energy. If you're struggling to lose weight in a healthy diet that an exercise isn't enough,
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): lean is for you get started with 20 off just use code candace 20 at take lean.com that's code candace 20 at take lean.com again take lean.com results vary these statements have not been evaluated by the fda and is not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease and is not a substitute
for care
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): from a health care provider donald trump
Speaker 10: is coming out hot after big pharma
Speaker 10: And he's, you know, had some rhetoric and he's had some stuff to say about pricing for a while, but he just recently dropped a new executive order that as far as I can tell is like a silver bullet against big pharma that is going to take away a huge amount of their revenue stream as well as a kneecap, an entire shadow industry that is the PBMs that just siphons money out
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): from in between as a middleman in the pharma world.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): It is now on the White House website officially, today's executive order. And if you read in section five, it details specifically
Speaker 10: what it calls most favored nation price targets. And this is something that Trump has referenced before,
but it
Speaker 10: has never really gotten, he never was able to get it through. And there you can see at the bottom of the first paragraph, communicate most favored nation price targets to pharmaceutical manufacturers to bring prices for American patients in line with comparably developed vaccines.
Speaker 10: nations. Now, when Trump put out a true social post about this just the other day, he said, we're going to bring the prices down to the
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): lowest of any nation there is. Meaning that if in Zimbabwe, they're paying a dollar per pill, then in America, we pay only a dollar per pill, whatever the lowest price around the world is. That language has been modified a little bit so that in the actual executive order, now Americans are mandated apparently to, we get to pay whatever the lowest price of any other developed nation.
Speaker 10: Which is awesome, because right now, we're getting grifted so hard. Right now, Americans are paying more than just about
any other
Speaker 10: nation in the world, often by multiples of 2, 5, or even 10x what other countries are paying for the exact same products. Also, in Section 4, he seems to enable direct-to-consumer sales from the pharmaceutical manufacturers at the most favored nation price, which is really interesting.
Speaker 10: Because, I mean, let's just say I've never been there. I'm no pharmaceutical
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): expert. But from what I'm reading there, that seems to be very much a death blow to a vast portion of pharma's profits. And,
I mean, I don't know
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): what to make of that
Speaker 10: other than extreme optimism. Because that's not all.
He also is
Speaker 10: going after the PBMs, the Pharmacy Benefit Managers.
He
Speaker 10: ordered RFK to facilitate programs for pharma manufacturers to sell direct consumers at the best nation price. If you're not familiar, these PBMs, pharmacy benefit managers, they're companies that manage prescription drug benefits and health insurers and employers. And they just kind of like middleman in between the whole system. And they just take a huge cut out from the middle, like an insanely huge cut.
Speaker 10: PBMs are over a trillion dollars a year in combined revenue, according to an FTC report, I think from last year, um, maybe from 2023. Um, so I mean,
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): a lot's going on here and I'm sure that a lot of people far smarter than me will have all kinds of takes, but I'd be surprised if anyone has any take that is not positive because I mean, we all love big pharma, right? So anyways, speaking of drugs, again,
Thank you.
A couple
Speaker 10: of the big boys got caught, allegedly, with a little baggie of drugs. But is that really the story that's going on here? I'm sure you've seen by now. I mean, if you have an X account, you've definitely seen. And if you don't have an X account, you've still probably seen. Macron just squirreling away the little bag of whiteness on his table and all that stuff that's been taken over the internet. And everyone's making funny memes and AI videos of them dancing and
Speaker 10: whatever else and yeah he grabs his little bag and sleuths it away but like let's just let's just pump the brakes for a second here guys it it might be a tissue like it really might be a tissue and like
maybe
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): it's a bag of drugs like a really big bag of drugs like just so like that's
a lot
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): of drugs and uh just on the like maybe
Speaker 10: We'll be right back.
But
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): regardless,
Speaker 10: even if it's a bag of drugs or it's a tissue, you can argue about that all day long. And yeah, it's a funny scandal, whatever. But, um, that's Emmanuel Macron. And if you don't recall, um, he's married to a dude.
And in case you're not
Speaker 10: up to date on the story and all the other implications of that story, um.
There's a
Speaker 10: whole series that Candace Owens made on this very YouTube channel that you could watch yourself and you might learn all about how Emmanuel Macron married his much, much, much older teacher that was not always a woman and might have even possibly one day been in his very same family.
That seems a
Speaker 10: lot more scandalous than world leaders doing cocaine, which I'm sure they probably all do. And
they might
Speaker 10: even all do right before the media comes into their room to do interviews
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): with them. We've all seen the images or the videos of Zelensky and Ardern just going all sniffly
Speaker 10: sniffly. We've seen it, and I'm sure it's happening. But ultimately...
The
Speaker 10: scandal is that he's married to a dude and that that implies all sorts of other things that we want answers to. So, yeah,
that's the story
Speaker 10: about the drugs. It's fun, but let's
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): be real. It
kind of feels like a
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): distraction, guys. Let's keep our eyes on the bigger prize, like the Illuminati controlling the world through a crazy call. I'm sorry. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
Speaker 10: Anyways.
that's
Speaker 10: about it for our episode today I think that about wraps us up I really appreciate you guys coming to hang out I really appreciate the whole team bringing me in and welcoming me to the studio I cannot wait to learn from them to learn from all the crazy rabbit holes that they've been down and to share them all with you if you haven't already remembered please like the video share the video subscribe to the
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): channel and I'll make sure that Candice comes and pops in to say hi before too long here but for now I'll
see you next time.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): Have a great night and we'll see you tomorrow.